<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide Bucharest</string>

    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="night_life">Night Life</string>
    <string name="location_image">Location Image</string>

    <string name="national_museum_art">National Museum of Art of Romania</string>
    <string name="national_museum_art_desc">The National Museum of Art of Romania (Romanian: Muzeul Național de Artă al României) is located in the Royal Palace in Revolution Square, central Bucharest. It features collections of medieval and modern Romanian art, as well as the international collection assembled by the Romanian royal family.</string>
    <string name="national_museum_art_address">Calea Victoriei 49&#8211;53, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="national_museum_art_hours">Wednesday to Sunday 10:00 to 18:00</string>
    <string name="national_museum_art_contact">021 313 3030</string>

    <string name="art_collections_museum">Art Collections Museum</string>
    <string name="art_collections_museum_desc">Inaugurated in 1978 as a Department of the
        National Museum of Art of Romania, the Art Collections Museum showcases artistic interests
        that prevailed in Romanian society from the early 20th century onward. Over 30 collections
        on permanent display incorporate a variety of art pieces and collectibles, ranging from
        Romanian and European fine and decorative arts to Oriental art. Donated over nearly a
        century by both collectors and artists, they bear witness to their owners’ taste and
        economic power, their leaning toward famous names or contemporary art, as well as to the
        artists particular interests, surroundings, and daily studio practice.</string>
    <string name="art_collections_museum_address">Calea Victoriei 111, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="art_collections_museum_hours">Wednesday to Sunday 11:00 to 19:00</string>
    <string name="art_collections_museum_contact">+4021 211 1749</string>
    
    <string name="k_m_zambaccian">K. H. Zambaccian Museum</string>
    <string name="k_m_zambaccian_desc">The museum brings centre stage a core selection of paintings
        by Theodor Pallady. Together with over 800 prints and drawings from the artist’s Parisian
        years, these are part of the Serafina and Gheorghe Răut collection, donated to the Romanian
        state at the end of the 1960s. The collection also comprises French, Dutch, English and
        Spanish paintings, European furniture and sculpture and a host of various objets d’art
        which speak eloquently about the manner in which Romanian inter-war intellectuals tried to
        emulate general trends. ‘ The museum is hosted in the Melik House. A traditional merchant
        house, built in the second half of the 18th century, it is one of the earliest surviving
        examples of vernacular Bucharest architecture and the only one open to the public.
        The house is named after its most important owner, Iacob Melik, a strong supporter of the
        1848 revolutionary movement, author of L’Orient devant L’Occident. While refurbishing the
        house, he keenly maintained traditional elements such as the first-floor verandah, the
        staircase and the wide eaves.</string>
    <string name="k_m_zambaccian_address">Muzeul Zambaccian 21 A, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="k_m_zambaccian_hours">Wednesday to Sunday 10:00 to 18:00</string>
    <string name="k_m_zambaccian_contact">+4021 230 1920</string>
    
    <string name="theodor_pallady">Theodor Pallady Museum</string>
    <string name="theodor_pallady_desc">The museum brings centre stage a core selection of
        paintings by Theodor Pallady. Together with over 800 prints and drawings from the artist’s
        Parisian years, these are part of the Serafina and Gheorghe Răut collection, donated to the
        Romanian state at the end of the 1960s. The collection also comprises French, Dutch,
        English and Spanish paintings, European furniture and sculpture and a host of various
        objets d’art which speak eloquently about the manner in which Romanian inter-war
        intellectuals tried to emulate general trends.</string>
    <string name="theodor_pallady_address">Spatarului 22, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="theodor_pallady_hours">Wednesday to Sunday 10:00 to 18:00</string>
    <string name="theodor_pallady_contact">+4021 211 4979</string>

    <string name="national_museum_romanian_history">National Museum of Romanian History</string>
    <string name="national_museum_romanian_history_desc">The National Museum of Romanian History
        (Romanian: Muzeul Național de Istorie a României) is a museum located on Calea Victoriei
        in Bucharest, Romania, which contains Romanian historical artifacts from prehistoric
        times up to modern times. The museum is located inside the former Postal Services Palace,
        which also houses a philatelic museum. With a surface of over 8,000 square meters, the
        museum has approx. 60 valuable exhibition rooms. The permanent displays include a plaster
        cast of the entirety of Trajan's Column, the Romanian Crown Jewels, and the Pietroasele
        treasure.</string>
    <string name="national_museum_romanian_history_address">Calea Victoriei 12, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="national_museum_romanian_history_hours">Wednesday to Sunday 10:00 to 18:00</string>
    <string name="national_museum_romanian_history_contact">+4021 315 8207</string>

    <string name="theodor_aman">Theodor Aman Museum</string>
    <string name="theodor_aman_desc">The Theodor Aman Museum is one of the most beautiful private
        residences in Bucharest, built in the year 1868 following Theodor Aman’s own designs. It is
        also one of the few buildings which has remained unchanged during its existence, and is the
        first workshop-residence in Romania. From the architectural plans of the house and exterior
        decorations (done in colaboration with sculptor Karl Storck) to the interior design
        (mural paintings, stained glass, stucco ceilings, wooden panelling in the workshop, and the
        house’s furniture), the house reflects Theodor Aman’s vision. The Theodor Aman Museum was
        opened in 1908 and is one of the oldest memorial museums in Romania. The house maintains
        its intimate atmosphere, gained during the Belle Époque period, and holds a large part of
        painter Theodor Aman’s works.</string>
    <string name="theodor_aman_address">C. A. Rosetti 8, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="theodor_aman_hours">Wednesday to Sunday 10:00 to 18:00</string>
    <string name="theodor_aman_contact">+4021 314 5812</string>

    <string name="peasant_museum">Romanian Peasant Museum</string>
    <string name="peasant_museum_desc">The National Museum of the Romanian Peasant (Romanian:
        Muzeul Național al Ţăranului Român) is a museum in Bucharest, Romania, with a collection
        of textiles (especially costumes), icons, ceramics, and other artifacts of Romanian
        peasant life. One of Europe\'s leading museums of popular arts and traditions, it was
        designated "European Museum of the Year" for 1996.</string>
    <string name="peasant_museum_address">Soseaua Pavel Dimitrievici Kiseleff 3, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="peasant_museum_hours">Tuesday to Sunday 09:00 to 17:00</string>
    <string name="peasant_museum_contact">+4021 317 9661</string>

    <string name="sutu_palace">Romanian Peasant Museum</string>
    <string name="sutu_palace_desc">Suţu Palace is one of the oldest aristocratic residences in
        Bucharest, as well as one of the very few buildings which have remained unchanged for over
        150 years. It was built between 1833 and 1835 by Costache Suţu, according to the designs
        of architects Conrad Schwink and Johann Veit. The palace\’s interior was designed in 1862
        by Karl Storck, renowned sculptor and decorative artist. He is responsible for the
        monumental double-winder set of stairs leading to the first floor, and for adding a
        beautiful gilded-frame mirror, brought all the way from Murano, Italy. The sculpted
        wooden medallion representing Irina Suţu, the owner\’s spouse, rests right above the
        mirror.</string>
    <string name="sutu_palace_address">Bulevardul Ion C. Bratianu 2, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="sutu_palace_hours">Tuesday to Sunday 10:00 to 18:00</string>
    <string name="sutu_palace_contact">+4021 315 6858</string>

    <string name="herastrau_park">King Michael I of Romania Park</string>
    <string name="herastrau_park_desc">King Michael I of Romania Park is a large park
        on the northern side of Bucharest, Romania, around Lake Herastrau, one of the lakes formed
        by the Colentina River. The park has an area of about 187 ha, of which 74 ha is the lake.
        Initially, the area was full of marshes, but these were drained between 1930 and 1935, and
        the park was opened in 1936. The park is divided into two zones: a rustic or natural zone
        (the Village Museum), which is left more or less undisturbed, and a public/'active' domain
        with open areas for recreation activities. Small boats are allowed on the lake.</string>
    <string name="herastrau_park_address">Parcul Regele Mihai I al Romaniei, Bucharest</string>

    <string name="tei_park">Tei Park</string>
    <string name="tei_park_desc">The main attraction of the park is the Ferris wheel, which is 63
        meters tall and counts 44 cabins. Other entertainment options in the park are the 15-meter
        tall roller coaster, the electric cars, a swings area, slides and inflatable mattresses.
        A smaller Ferris wheel exists in the park. It 12 cabins which lift 16 meters high. The
        entire park features areas themed after various tales.</string>
    <string name="tei_park_address">Parcul Lacul Tei, Bucharest</string>
    
    <string name="circus_park">Circus Park</string>
    <string name="circus_park_desc">A rather unknown park for foreign tourists in Bucharest,
        the Circus Park is a fine, green location in the Romanian capital when you need a few
        relaxing hours, or when you need to stop a little and have a coffee or anything else to
        drink while you visit the city. In the middle of the park is located the headquarters of
        Globus Circus, the building being surrounded by trees, alleys and lawns, just perfect to
        take a walk, away from the noisy city.</string>
    <string name="circus_park_address">Parcul Circului, Bulevardul Lacul Tei, Bucharest</string>

    <string name="caru_cu_bere">Caru\' cu bere</string>
    <string name="caru_cu_bere_desc">At the foundation of Caru’ cu bere’s identity lays a history
        of more than 130 years,  starting with the Mircea brothers, among which Mircea Nicolae as
        the founder, his legacy and the historical building. The place which keeps immortal the
        spirit of old Bucharest: Caru’ cu bere (The beer wagon)</string>
    <string name="caru_cu_bere_address">Strada Stavropoleos 5, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="caru_cu_bere_hours">Monday to Sunday 08:00 to 24:00</string>
    <string name="caru_cu_bere_contact">+4021 313 7560</string>

    <string name="mesogios">Mesogios</string>
    <string name="mesogios_desc">Mesogios is the right place for seafood lovers, because they can
        choose their main course from the fish display, right at the entrance. We call it
        gastronomy voyeurism and it is our trademark. We want to show the clients, right from the
        very first moment, that they can only find fresher seafood if they fish it themselves.
        After they choose the main course, our chefs cook it however the client wants. We are
        located in the most beautiful area of Bucharest, near Herastrau Park, the biggest and
        most popular park in Bucharest, in a high class neighborhood where former dictator
        Ceausescu used to live. At Mesogios you will savor delicious dishes in an elegant and
        intimate atmosphere where we hope you will feel like home.</string>
    <string name="mesogios_address">Helesteului 30, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="mesogios_hours">Monday to Sunday 13:30 to 24:00</string>
    <string name="mesogios_contact">+40722 200 232</string>

    <string name="casa_doina">Casa Doina</string>
    <string name="casa_doina_desc">In 2003 The Street Tavern takes on a new identity - Casa Doina -
        but keeps all of its old habits. While a few modern ammenities have been added, you still
        feel like you are walking into another place in time, after a long carriage trip you lay
        down your top hat and stop for a refreshing drink or for a late supper.</string>
    <string name="casa_doina_address">Kiseleff 4, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="casa_doina_hours">Monday to Sunday 11:00 to 23:00</string>
    <string name="casa_doina_contact">+4021 222 6717</string>

    <string name="excalibur">Excalibur</string>
    <string name="excalibur_desc">Have you ever dreamed of at a feast where relaxation and mood
        are beyond the false rules of etiquette? In a very special place, cuted off from everyday
        reality, the delicacies are saturated and the medieval scent of the place makes you want
        to feast with your hand, because this is the only way you can really enjoy a royal
        cuisine? Excalibur restaurant is the only place in Bucharest where succulent steaks,
        tasty pies and vintage wines are served in generous portions, as in the days of
        King Arthur by knights and ladies for wich the honor and reputation are above all.
        We welcome you to visit us for a special medieval experience!</string>
    <string name="excalibur_address">Academiei 39, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="excalibur_hours">Monday to Sunday 12:00 to 24:00</string>
    <string name="excalibur_contact">+4021 314 5670</string>

    <string name="mojo">Mojo</string>
    <string name="mojo_desc">Of all the pubs and live music clubs in the Old Town, this is the one
        you want to come to. Set over three levels there is something for just about everyone.
        Upstairs you have the best karaoke bar in the city - every night from 21:00 - while the
        ground floor pub is packed with big screens showing any sport that matters, including
        English football via Sky and BT Sports. Downstairs, the cavernous cellar hosts live music.
        All the drinks are a good price, served by decent bar staff who will not keep you waiting.
        Regular live stand-up comedy in both Romanian and English, and the Big British Bucharest
        Quiz is held here every other Wednesday.</string>
    <string name="mojo_address">Gabroveni 14 , Bucharest</string>
    <string name="mojo_hours">Monday to Sunday 13:00 to 05:00</string>
    <string name="mojo_contact">+40737 220 220</string>

    <string name="queens">Queens</string>
    <string name="queens_desc">While Romania is still a somewhat intolerant country when it comes
        to gay rights, things are changing slowly. The presence of this club in the city centre
        is evidence of that. Every Friday and Saturday night Queens welcomes girls and boys of all
        persuasions, and usually puts on some kind of live show - often a no-holds-barred affair
        - at least once a week.</string>
    <string name="queens_address">B-dul Carol 61, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="queens_hours">Friday to Saturday 10:00 to 05:00</string>
    <string name="queens_contact">+40721 012 100</string>

    <string name="craft_beer">Romanian Craft Beer Bar</string>
    <string name="craft_beer_desc">Fantastic craft beer pub on Bucharest\'s most famous street,
        run by the people behind Zaganu, the original Romanian craft beer, brewed at Maneciu
        Ungureni since 2013. They have since launched four further beers: a brown ale, an IPA,
        a red ale and Adonis, a limited edition pale ale. This place though is not just about
        Zaganu: you will also find many other locally-brewed beers, from most of the other 15
        or so craft beer producers who have cropped up over the past couple of years. Fabrica
        always has at least ten beers on tap and loads more bottled. One of our fave places in
        the Romanian capital.</string>
    <string name="craft_beer_address">Calea Victoriei 91, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="craft_beer_hours">Monday to Saturday 12:00 to 2345</string>
    <string name="craft_beer_contact">+40770 550 234</string>

    <string name="stpatrick">St. Patrick</string>
    <string name="stpatrick_desc">Looks like a pub, feels like a pub, even smells like a pub. This
        is a big, well located and quite frankly brilliant venue in the Old Town area: it really
        sets the standard for the many others in the area. Set over two levels every inch of this
        place is a proper boozer serving exemplary Guinness and Kilkenny on tap alongside loads
        of decent beers and good pub grub. Also has what is probably the largest collection of
        single malts in the country. Staff are good and ensure that you do not have to wait long
        for a drink. Look out for the St. Patrick Party Room on the other side of the street: a
        kind of Have We Got More St. Patrick For You. Quirky and cool.</string>
    <string name="stpatrick_address">Smardan 23, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="stpatrick_hours">Monday to Sunday 12:00 to 02:00</string>
    <string name="stpatrick_contact">+4021 314 5670</string>

    <string name="drunken_lords">The Drunken Lords</string>
    <string name="drunken_lords_desc">On a narrow side street which links Strada Lipscani with
        Strada Blanari (right in the heart of the Old Town) you will find this popular venue:
        a good, lively pub and club playing decent music and offering a vibe a little more
        upmarket than most other places in the area. Hosts plenty of live music, sports and
        regular cultural events. The entire wall of one side opens up during good weather,
        allowing everyone to gather outside for a drink, smoke and a chat. Prices and service
        are well above average. You\'ll like the place.</string>
    <string name="drunken_lords_address">Nicolae Selari 3, Bucharest</string>
    <string name="drunken_lords_hours">Monday to Sunday 12:00 to 05:00</string>
    <string name="drunken_lords_contact">+40736 238 815</string>

</resources>
